{
  "CS2205": {
    "UNIT1": [
      {
        "question": "The three-tier model is a",
        "choices": [
          "a.\nsoftware architecture",
          "b.\nsoftware architecture and a software design pattern.",
          "c.\nsoftware design pattern."
        ],
        "answer": "software architecture and a software design pattern."
      },
      {
        "question": "On a dynamic web site, the content on the server is the same, but instead of just being HTML, it also contains dynamic code, which may display different data depending on information you feed to the web site",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "A number of browsers will come with some plugins pre-installed, so you may not be aware that content is being displayed via a plugin and not natively within the browser.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "JavaScript is the scripting language that you use to add behaviour to your web pages",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "PHP, Python, Ruby on Rails, ASP.NET , Coldfusion are examples of ____________ languages",
        "answer": "Dynamic"
      },
      {
        "question": "Three-tier architecture has the following three tiers:",
        "answer": "b. Presentation tier, Application tier and Data tier"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which one of the following is true ?",
        "answer": "c. In HTML Certain elements don’t need a closing tag, in XHTML all elements must be explicitly closed."
      },
      {
        "question": "Tim Berners-Lee had been working on a information management system, in which text could contain links and references to other works, allowing the reader to quickly jump from document to document",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "Cascading Style Sheets give you complete control over how an element is displayed.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "13) One reason for following Web Standards is Device Compatibility",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "CSS can be checked out using the CSS validator available at http://jigsaw.w3.org/css-validator/",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "Netscape and ___(a)____ each tried to get a competitive edge in terms of the features they supported in order to attract developers. This has since become known as the ___(b)___ wars.",
        "answer": "c. (a) Microsoft (b) browser"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is true",
        "answer": "c. You do not have to have Internet connectivity to build a web site in HTML"
      },
      {
        "question": "The easiest way to check for standards compliance is to use a handy tool, available online, called a validator. The World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) makes a validator freely available at http://validator.w3.org/ . You can (and should) use this tool to check any web sites you’re developing for errors in your",
        "answer": "a. HTML/XHTML"
      },
      {
        "question": "Three-tier is a client–server architecture in which",
        "answer": "the user interface, functional process logic (\"business rules\"), computer data storage and data access are developed and maintained as independent modules"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a web browser?",
        "answer": "d. Twitter"
      },
      {
        "question": "Sometimes, when browsing the Internet, you’ll come across web pages that don’t have an .html extension—they might have a .php, .asp, .aspx, .jsp, or some other extension. These are all examples of static web technologies.",
        "answer": "False"
      }
    ],
    "UNIT2": [
      {
        "question": "Concerning typography",
        "answer": "c. The most effective way to control how typography looks on a web page is through using Cascading Style Sheet."
      },
      {
        "question": "Last year, 30% of winning intranets had a mobile version. This year, 60% of winners had a mobile intranet. Doubling in one year is truly a sign that mobile access is a huge trend right now.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "Fortunately, a designer can add colour to a site without losing accessibility and usability if the site is designed with those capabilities in mind. While many designers feel comfortable designing a site for many users, those same designers might feel inadequate when it comes to choosing colours and graphics.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "Concerning navigation",
        "answer": "a. One of the most crucial aspects of successful site navigation is consistency"
      },
      {
        "question": "Concerning the Home Page, which of the following is true",
        "answer": "d. It is a common misconception to think that the home page is the first page your site visitors will see."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is true",
        "answer": "b. The primary colours consist of red, yellow and blue, and they’re called primary colours because you don’t need to mix colours to make these three hues."
      },
      {
        "question": "A triadic colour scheme is created",
        "answer": "c. when you pick one colour and then pick two other colours that lie equidistant from each other around the circle"
      },
      {
        "question": "In testing mobile websites on mobile devices, we found that sites with fewer features have much better usability than full-featured websites. This year's winning mobile intranets followed this recommendation, focusing on specific features that were important to employees on the go instead of trying to squeeze the entire intranet onto a tiny screen.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "most web designers limit themselves to the most commonly-available fonts across all systems, which are usually limited to the following:",
        "answer": "c. Andale Mono, Times New Roman, Georgia, Verdana, Arial/Arial Black, Courier/Courier New, Trebuchet MS, Comic Sans (this is an unprofessional, many would say ugly font—don’t use this, except perhaps sparingly on sites aimed at children)."
      },
      {
        "question": "The home page should, at least provide the following:",
        "answer": "b. define the main goal of the site and provide an overview, show what’s new, introduce the brand, provide navigation to other areas of the site."
      },
      {
        "question": "Systems that force people to create content from scratch, every time promotes and encourages user participation.",
        "answer": "False"
      },
      {
        "question": "When designing a website, the golden rule is that \"content is king!\" No matter how flashy and colorful a website is, it is virtually useless without organized, accessible content. This means that a person searching for information must be able to quickly find it on your website. If not, they will leave.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "Although Nielsen’s philosophy of bare-bones Web architecture has accessibility and usability merits, most Web designers want to add a signature touch to their sites with many design elements",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "Most web designers limit themselves to the most commonly-available fonts across all systems, which are usually limited to the following:",
        "answer": "c. Andale Mono, Times New Roman, Georgia, Verdana, Arial/Arial Black, Courier/Courier New, Trebuchet MS, Comic Sans (this is an unprofessional, many would say ugly font—don’t use this, except perhaps sparingly on sites aimed at children)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Sometimes, knowledge sharing can be as simple as a Q&A tool to connect employees with questions to colleagues with answers.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is true",
        "answer": "b. As long as there is an apparent progress from one link to the next, and the indication is that they are still on track to reach their end goal, users will tend to continue through a site."
      },
      {
        "question": "Whilst it may be tempting to cram in a little of everything on the home page, it is actually better to use it to highlight other areas of content within the site and drive your traffic to them.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is true",
        "answer": "c. A good technique is to search the web for other websites in your line of business. Take a look at their design, content and navigation for ideas as how to organize the content of your website."
      },
      {
        "question": "Once users “learn” how to use a site, they usually don’t like to see changes from page to page",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "If you want more help deciding whether the colours you've chosen provide a good enough contrast, try out a",
        "answer": "c. Contrast Analyser tool. This tool checks the contrast between foreground and background colours."
      },
      {
        "question": "To start designing business Web sites, you should collect information on what the client wants on their site and how it should be structured, what kind of branding that company uses, and then use that information to build up a visual design mockup that you can agree with the client before you add graphics and colour schemes on to it.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "14) Complementary colour schemes are great to use in web sites, as they also contain both warm and cool colours.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "Fortunately, a designer can add colour to a site without losing accessibility and usability if the site is designed with those capabilities in mind. While many designers feel comfortable designing a site for many users, those same designers might feel inadequate when it comes to choosing colours and graphics.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "Systems that force people to create content from scratch, every time promotes and encourages user participation.",
        "answer": "False"
      },
      {
        "question": "most web designers limit themselves to the most commonly-available fonts across all systems, which are usually limited to the following:",
        "answer": "c. Andale Mono, Times New Roman, Georgia, Verdana, Arial/Arial Black, Courier/Courier New, Trebuchet MS, Comic Sans (this is an unprofessional, many would say ugly font—don’t use this, except perhaps sparingly on sites aimed at children)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Concerning the Home Page, which of the following is true",
        "answer": "c. Andale Mono, Times New Roman, Georgia, Verdana, Arial/Arial Black, Courier/Courier New, Trebuchet MS, Comic Sans (this is an unprofessional, many would say ugly font—don’t use this, except perhaps sparingly on sites aimed at children)."
      },
      {
        "question": "Although Nielsen’s philosophy of bare-bones Web architecture has accessibility and usability merits, most Web designers want to add a signature touch to their sites with many design elements",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "In testing mobile websites on mobile devices, we found that sites with fewer features have much better usability than full-featured websites. This year's winning mobile intranets followed this recommendation, focusing on specific features that were important to employees on the go instead of trying to squeeze the entire intranet onto a tiny screen.",
        "answer": "True"
      }
    ],
    "UNIT3": [
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is true",
        "answer": "b. A markup language is a set of markup tags. HTML tags are keywords surrounded by angle brackets like"
      },
      {
        "question": "HTML tags are not case sensitive: <P> means the same as <p>. Many web sites use uppercase HTML tags. We recommend and use lowercase tags because the World Wide Web Consortium (W3C) recommends lowercase in HTML 4, and demands lowercase tags in XHTML.",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "Header information in a table is defined with the <th> tag. A <td> tag can contain text, links, images, lists, forms, but not other tables",
        "answer": "False"
      },
      {
        "question": "HTML documents consist of nested HTML elements",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is true\na) HTML headings are defined with the <h1> to <h6> tags.\nb) HTML headings are defined with the <h0> to <h6> tags.\nc) HTML headings are defined with the <h1> to <h5> tags.\nd) HTML headings are defined with the <h1> to <h7> tags.",
        "answer": "a"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is true\na) The <p> element defines a paragraph in the HTML document.\nThe element has only a start tag <p>; also the <br>tag defines a\nline break, and does not have a closing tag\nb) The <p> element defines a paragraph in the HTML document.\nThe element has a start tag <p> and an end tag </p>. The\n<br>tag defines a line break, and has also the closing tag </br>.\nc) The <p> element defines a paragraph in the HTML document.\nThe element has only the start tag <p> however the <br> tag\nwhich defines a line break has also the closing tag </br>\nd) The <p> element defines a paragraph in the HTML document.\nThe element has a start tag <p> and an end tag </p>. The\n<br>tag defines a line break, and does not have a closing tag",
        "answer": "d"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is true",
        "answer": "c. When you save an HTML file, you can use either the .htm or the .html file extension. There is no difference, it is entirely up to you."
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is true",
        "answer": "a. HTML elements can have attributes. Attributes provide additional information about an element. Attributes are always specified in the start tag. Attributes come in name/value pairs like: name=\"value\""
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is true\na) HTML links are defined with the <at> tag and HTML images are\ndefined with the <img> tag.\nb) HTML links are defined with the <a> tag and HTML images are\ndefined with the <imge> tag.\nc) HTML links are defined with the <al> tag and HTML images are\ndefined with the <img> tag.\nd) HTML links are defined with the <a> tag and HTML images are\ndefined with the <img> tag.",
        "answer": "d"
      },
      {
        "question": "HTML documents are also called web pages",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is true",
        "answer": "c. HTML stands for Hyper Text Markup Language is a language for describing web pages and not a programming language"
      },
      {
        "question": "The <tbody> tag is used to group the body content in an HTML table. The tbody element should be used in conjunction with the thead and tfoot elements",
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "Header information in a table are defined with the <th> tag. A <td> tag can contain text, links, images, lists, forms, but not other tables",
        "answer": "False"
      }
    ],
    "UNIT4": [
      {
        "question": "",
        "answer": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "",
        "answer": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "",
        "answer": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "",
        "answer": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "",
        "answer": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "",
        "answer": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "",
        "answer": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "",
        "answer": ""
      },
      {
        "question": "",
        "answer": ""
      }
    ]
  }
}
